Guide to the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 records, 1910-2009; 5739-001; 26.52 cubic feet 31 boxes
  - Series III: Contract Negotiations, 1950-2009 (Box-folder 16/1-16/47; 17/1-17/61; 18/1-18/40; 19/1-19/43; 21/1-21/94; 22/1-22/68; 23/1-23/78; 24/1-24/74; 25/1-25/86; 26/1-26/97; 27/1-27/73; 28/1-28/101; 29/1-29/94; 30/1-30/64)
    - Subseries B: Contract Negotiations Part 2, 1952-2009 (Box-folder 21/1-21/94; 22/1-22/68; 23/1-23/78; 24/1-24/74; 25/1-25/86; 26/1-26/97; 27/1-27/73; 28/1-28/101; 29/1-29/94; 30/1-30/64)
      - Frahler Electric Co., Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2005 (Box-folder 25/31)
      - Frahler Electric Co., Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2005 (Box-folder 25/32)
      - Fraser Boiler & Ship Repair, LLC Contract Negotiations, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 25/33)
      - Frederick & Nelson (Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 1965-1987 (Box-folder 25/34)
      - French's Electric Service Contract Negotiations, 1960-1978 (Box-folder 25/35)
      - Friberg Electric Co. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 25/36)
      - Frontier Electric, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1978 (Box-folder 25/37)
      - Fryer-Knowles, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1995 (Box-folder 25/38)
      - Futurecom Technologies (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2002-2008 (Box-folder 25/39)
      - Garmire Electric Company (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 25/40)
      - Gateway Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1985-1993 (Box-folder 25/41)
      - GC Electric LLC (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2009 (Box-folder 25/42)
      - Gemini Electric, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1974-1985 (Box-folder 25/43)
      - General Electric Company Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1957-1971 (Box-folder 25/44)
      - General Electric Company Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1957-1971 (Box-folder 25/45)
      - General Electric (Oil Burner) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 25/46)
      - General Service Electric, Inc. - National Electrical Contractors Association (NECA) Contract Negotiations, 1961-1982 (Box-folder 25/47)
      - Genesee Fuel and Heating Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 25/48)
      - Gerke's Appliance Co. Contract Negotiations, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 25/49)
      - G. H. Star Electric (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 25/50)
      - Glendale Oil Company Contract Negotiations, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 25/51)
      - Global Electric Contract Negotiations, 1981 (Box-folder 25/52)
      - Globe Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990-2001 (Box-folder 25/53)
      - Globe Electric, Inc. (Marine) Contract Negotiations, 1992 (Box-folder 25/54)
      - Globe Electric, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1990 (Box-folder 25/55)
      - Goedert's Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 25/56)
      - Golden Electric, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 25/57)
      - Gracey Electric Service (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1992 (Box-folder 25/58)
      - Gracey Electric Service (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1992 (Box-folder 25/59)
      - Great Oaks Construction, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 25/60)
      - Greenwood Motor Shop Contract Negotiations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 25/61)
      - Griffen Fuel Company of Seattle Contract Negotiations, 1966-1976, 1993 (Box-folder 25/62)
      - Groff Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1967-1989 (Box-folder 25/63)
      - Grove's City Electric Service, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 25/64)
      - Haaland Associates, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 25/65)
      - Hagen Electric (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1973-1986 (Box-folder 25/66)
      - Hamby Marine Electric Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1979 (Box-folder 25/67)
      - Hamilton Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 25/68)
      - Hampton Electric Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 25/69)
      - Hansen Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998 (Box-folder 25/70)
      - Hanson Controls Contract Negotiations, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 25/71)
      - Harbor Electrical Co. - D.W. Close - National Electrical Contractors Association (NECA) (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 25/72)
      - Harbor Electric Service Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1973-1985 (Box-folder 25/73)
      - Harry's Radio and T.V. Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1971-1983 (Box-folder 25/74)
      - Harry's Radio and T.V. Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1971-1983 (Box-folder 25/75)
      - Hatch Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1961-1984 (Box-folder 25/76)
      - Hatfield Electric Co. Contract Negotiations, 1987 (Box-folder 25/77)
      - Hawthorne Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2005-2009 (Box-folder 25/78)
      - Hawthorne Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2005 (Box-folder 25/79)
      - HBC Electrical Contractors, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 25/80)
      - Heartfelt Communications (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 25/81)
      - Heath-Northwest, Inc. (Neon Manufacturing) Contract Negotiations, 1969-1984 (Box-folder 25/82)
      - Heckendorf Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 25/83)
      - H. E. Mills Electric Company (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1986, 1997-2005 (Box-folder 25/84)
      - H. E. Mills Electric Company (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1997 (Box-folder 25/85)
      - Hendricks Electric Co. Contract Negotiations, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 25/86)
      - Hennum Electric Service Contract Negotiations, 1961-1976 (Box-folder 26/1)
      - Hertz Electric Company, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 26/2)
      - Hewitt Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 26/3)
      - HGC Herndon General Contracting Contract Negotiations, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 26/4)
      - Hi-Line Group LLC (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2003-2009 (Box-folder 26/5)
      - Hillyard Heating Contract Negotiations, 1960-1976 (Box-folder 26/6)
      - Holert Electric, Inc. - National Electrical Contractors Association Contract Negotiations (NECA) Contract Negotiations, 1964-1978 (Box-folder 26/7)
      - Holmes-Burke, A Joint Venture (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 26/8)
      - Holmes-Burke, A Joint Venture (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 26/9)
      - Home Oil Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1974-1989 (Box-folder 26/10)
      - Homer E. Puariea Company - Security Fencing Trident Job Contract Negotiations, 1978 (Box-folder 26/11)
      - Home Technologies' Low Voltage Commercial Division (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2006-2009 (Box-folder 26/12)
      - Honeywell, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1976 (Box-folder 26/13)
      - Hospital Communications Systems, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 26/14)
      - Howard Electric Co. Contract Negotiations, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 26/15)
      - Howard E. Mills Electric Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 26/16)
      - Howe Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1978 (Box-folder 26/17)
      - Hughes Electrical Contractors, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 26/18)
      - Humphrey Radio & T.V. Contract Negotiations, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 26/19)
      - Hunnicut Electrical Contractors, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 26/20)
      - Hussman Northwest Contract Negotiations, 1961-1984 (Box-folder 26/21)
      - Icon Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 26/22)
      - Icon Electric, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 26/23)
      - I'ditarod Electric, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 26/24)
      - I.E.S., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1992 (Box-folder 26/25)
      - IMPCO Electric Co. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 26/26)
      - Indoor Climate Control Contract Negotiations, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 26/27)
      - Indu-Com Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 26/28)
      - Industrial Electric Co., Inc. - Everett Contract Negotiations, 1975 (Box-folder 26/29)
      - Industrial Electric Seattle, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1969-1994 (Box-folder 26/30)
      - Industrial Electric Seattle, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1969-1994 (Box-folder 26/31)
      - Industrial Power and Automation Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 26/32)
      - Industrial Power and Automation Co. (Light Fixture Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 26/33)
      - Industrial Power and Automation Co. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 26/34)
      - Industrial Power Contractors, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1983-1999 (Box-folder 26/35)
      - Inlet Electric USA, LLC Contract Negotiations, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 26/36)
      - Intercity Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2009 (Box-folder 26/37)
      - Interface Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 26/38)
      - Intermountain Electric Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 26/39)
      - International Control System, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 26/40)
      - International Control System, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1991 (Box-folder 26/41)
      - International Steel (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 26/42)
      - Issaquah Masonry, Electric & Fireplace Shop (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1982 (Box-folder 26/43)
      - Issaquah School District Contract Negotiations, 1971 (Box-folder 26/44)
      - JAFO, Inc. D/B/A Jim Fox Electric Co. Contract Negotiations, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 26/45)
      - James Electric Co. Contract Negotiations, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 26/46)
      - James Town Electric LLC D/B/A Sequoyah Electric LLC (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 26/47)
      - James Town Electric LLC D/B/A Sequoyah Electric LLC (Light Fixture Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 26/48)
      - James Town Electric LLC D/B/A Sequoyah Electric LLC (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 26/49)
      - James Town Electric LLC D/B/A Sequoyah Electric LLC (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 26/50)
      - James Town Electric LLC D/B/A Sequoyah Electric LLC (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 26/51)
      - J and J Electric of Indiana, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 26/52)
      - Jardeen Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1960-1991 (Box-folder 26/53)
      - Jarmuth Electric Contract Negotiations, 1961-1977 (Box-folder 26/54)
      - Jarvis Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 26/55)
      - JAS Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 26/56)
      - J.C. Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1979, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 26/57)
      - J.D.L. Electric Contract Negotiations, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 26/58)
      - J.L.F. Construction, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 26/59)
      - J.L.S. Electric Contract Negotiations, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 26/60)
      - JMK Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 26/61)
      - Joe Beattie Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 26/62)
      - Johansen Mechanical, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2005 (Box-folder 26/63)
      - Johansen Mechanical, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2000 (Box-folder 26/64)
      - John Burns Construction Company (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 26/65)
      - John Julian & Son Contract Negotiations, 1956-1967 (Box-folder 26/66)
      - Johnson Controls, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1966-1986 (Box-folder 26/67)
      - Johnson Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 26/68)
      - Johnson Yokogawa Corporation (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 26/69)
      - Jon-El Service Co. Contract Negotiations, 1976 (Box-folder 26/70)
      - J.S. Electric Co. Contract Negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 26/71)
      - JWP Systems (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 26/72)
      - K.A. Hovde Electrical Construction Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 26/73)
      - K.A. Hovde Electrical Construction Co., Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 26/74)
      - KDC Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 26/75)
      - Keizer Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 26/76)
      - K. J. Cole, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 26/77)
      - Keyte's Electric, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 26/78)
      - Keyte's Electric, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 26/79)
      - Ki Electrical Services (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 26/80)
      - Ki Electrical Services (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2007 (Box-folder 26/81)
      - Kingrex Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 26/82)
      - Kneal Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-2001 (Box-folder 26/83)
      - Kneal Electric, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 26/84)
      - Kneal Electric, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 26/85)
      - Knobel's Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1981-1992 (Box-folder 26/86)
      - KV Electric Corp. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 26/87)
      - KV Electric Corp. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 26/88)
      - KV Electric Corp. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 26/89)
      - K & W Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1996-2003 (Box-folder 26/90)
      - Lake Washington School District Contract Negotiations, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 26/91)
      - LAN Network Infrastructures (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2005 (Box-folder 26/92)
      - LAN Network Infrastructures (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 26/93)
      - Larry Gillespie Control Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 26/94)
      - Lazer Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1997-2006 (Box-folder 26/95)
      - Leaf Corporation Contract Negotiations, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 26/96)
      - Ledalite Architectural Products Corp. (Light Fixture Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 26/97)
      - Liberty Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1986-1997 (Box-folder 27/1)
      - Lighting & Grounding System, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990 (Box-folder 27/2)
      - Limited Energy (Sound & Communication) Systems Contract Negotiations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 27/3)
      - Lindberg Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1985-2003 (Box-folder 27/4)
      - L.K. Comstock (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2005 (Box-folder 27/5)
      - L & L Construction & Firestop (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 27/6)
      - Lloyd Electric Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 27/7)
      - Lloyd Electric Co., Inc. (Motor Shop) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 27/8)
      - Lloyd Electric Co., Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 27/9)
      - Loh's Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1993 (Box-folder 27/10)
      - LSK Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 27/11)
      - Luke's M & M Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1971-1997 (Box-folder 27/12)
      - Luke's M & M Electric, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 27/13)
      - Lumin Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 27/14)
      - Lumin Electric, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 27/15)
      - Lumin Electric, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 27/16)
      - Lunde Electric Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1995-2003 (Box-folder 27/17)
      - Lunde Electric Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1980-2002 (Box-folder 27/18)
      - L. W. McCandlish Electric Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 27/19)
      - MacDonald-Miller Co. (Light Fixture Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 1994 (Box-folder 27/20)
      - MacDonald-Miller Co. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 27/21)
      - Manley Service Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 27/22)
      - Marco Seattle, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 27/23)
      - Marine Electrical & Process Control, LLC (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 27/24)
      - Market Electric Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-2001 (Box-folder 27/25)
      - Market Electric Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 27/26)
      - Martin Selig Contract Negotiations, 1991 (Box-folder 27/27)
      - Masters Electrical & Communications, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1995-2003 (Box-folder 27/28)
      - Masters Electrical & Communications, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1995 (Box-folder 27/29)
      - Masters Electrical & Communications, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 27/30)
      - Masthead International, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1995 (Box-folder 27/31)
      - McConnell's Electrical Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1988-1995 (Box-folder 27/32)
      - McConnell's Electrical Co., Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 27/33)
      - Mc G Services Electric Construction Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 27/34)
      - Mercury Electric Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 27/35)
      - Merry Weather Associates (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 27/36)
      - Merry Weather Associates (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 27/37)
      - Metro Electric Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2001-2009 (Box-folder 27/38)
      - Metropolitan Electric, Inc. D/B/A City Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1963-1990 (Box-folder 27/39)
      - Meyer Sign Company (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 27/40)
      - Midland Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 27/41)
      - Midland Electric, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1990 (Box-folder 27/42)
      - Midland Electric, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 27/43)
      - Mike Evans & Associates Contract Negotiations, 1985-1997 (Box-folder 27/44)
      - Miller Audio (Sound & Communication), 1995 (Box-folder 27/45)
      - MJM Electrical Contractors (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 27/46)
      - Modern Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1996-2009 (Box-folder 27/47)
      - Modern Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1996 (Box-folder 27/48)
      - Molina Delta Electric Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 27/49)
      - Molina Delta Electric Co. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1998 (Box-folder 27/50)
      - Moorehead Electric Company, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 27/51)
      - Morningstar Electric Contract Negotiations, 1989 (Box-folder 27/52)
      - Mr. Electric West (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 27/53)
      - Music Room Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 27/54)
      - Music Room Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 27/55)
      - National Concrete Cutting (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1969-2005 (Box-folder 27/56)
      - National Mobile Television, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 27/57)
      - National Service Networks Communications (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1998 (Box-folder 27/58)
      - N-Control, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1995-2006 (Box-folder 27/59)
      - N-Control, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 27/60)
      - N.E. Construction (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 27/61)
      - Netswork, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 27/62)
      - Netversant Power Systems (Light Fixture Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 2002-2006 (Box-folder 27/63)
      - Netversant Technologies (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 27/64)
      - Netversant-Washington, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2003-2008 (Box-folder 27/65)
      - Netversant-Washington, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2008 (Box-folder 27/66)
      - Newhall Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 27/67)
      - New Horizons Telecom, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1996-2003 (Box-folder 27/68)
      - New Horizons Telecom, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 27/69)
      - New Horizons Telecom, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 27/70)
      - New Image Neon Contract Negotiations, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 27/71)
      - New Master Construction, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 27/72)
      - NMI Industrial Contractors (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 27/73)
      - North Range Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1997-2004 (Box-folder 28/1)
      - North Range Electric (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 28/2)
      - North Shore Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 28/3)
      - Northwest Cable News Contract Negotiations, 1998 (Box-folder 28/4)
      - Northwest Electric Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1964-1993 (Box-folder 28/5)
      - Northwest Electric Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1964-1993 (Box-folder 28/6)
      - Northwest Industrial Contractors, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 28/7)
      - Nova Telecommunications LLC (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2006 (Box-folder 28/8)
      - Ochs Brothers Heating (Oil Burner) Contract Negotiations, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 28/9)
      - O'Leary Electric Contract Negotiations, 1970-1985 (Box-folder 28/10)
      - Olson Fuel Company (Oil Burner) Contract Negotiations, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 28/11)
      - Olympia Electric Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 28/12)
      - Olympic Diesel Fuel Company Contract Negotiations, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 28/13)
      - Olympic Hotel Contract Negotiations, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 28/14)
      - Omega-Baja Industrial Contractors, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2003-2007 (Box-folder 28/15)
      - Omega Electric Corporate Security (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1996 (Box-folder 28/16)
      - Omega Industrial Contractors (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1997-2003 (Box-folder 28/17)